[{"answer": "Well, I think that is a big -- a big part of it.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "The point is the gun, isn't it?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Well, I believe life is the most precious right.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "-- which is do you agree with that Sandy Hook father's premise that the right of his child's life supersedes any rights under the Second Amendment to own a high-powered magazine or an assault rifle?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Well, I just first want to say thank you to Van Jones because I couldn't have said it better myself, and I agree with everything he said.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Kellyanne, I mean, unless I'm mistaken, you share the view that the NRA put out, which is that you don't solve the gun violence problem in America by reducing the number of guns?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "For me, that is also a no-brainer.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "The big question to me is, who is actually going to stand up and realize the more guns you have out there, the more gun violence?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, it's certainly good to hear that from the Jamaican government.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "I mean, is that the worst thing that could be said about a country?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "I'm fine.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Well, we won in the appellate court, a reversal of two of the four misdemeanor convictions, and Miss (INAUDIBLE) and I are preparing, even started today, we will be filing some more pleas in the appellate court seeking further relief to dismiss all of those remaining two charges.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "What can you tell me about those developments?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "I did watch the movie.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Did Casey see the movie?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "You know what, I don't -- I spoke with her.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "And did Casey herself see the movie, do you know?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Well, I guess there's so many things we have to worry about changing in society.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "How are you going to try and work through this in terms of client management and changing public perception?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "I mean, one of the ways, of course, could be that she gives an interview, perhaps to me on this show, and speaks honestly for an hour about her experience and tries to communicate with the American public who still doubt her innocence.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "How do you change people's mentalities about some things that they're just married to?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Obviously, the case, the trial tore them all apart, but has there been any repairing of the damage there?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "The best way I can describe it is with anxiety.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "How is she coping with this on a human level?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "She does not have current exposure.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "And if she does, what is the kind of reaction that she gets?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "You would do anything for your child, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "I think it's all mysterious.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Can you shed any light on this, David?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Yes, I think so.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Has she had another wardrobe malfunction?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "USSELL: I'm very proud of it.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "It's like the ultimate thing that you would wish for?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Hi.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "I'm going to have to read over them again but --", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Do you plead guilty to all those descriptions?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Well, unintentionally, yes, unfortunately.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Are you rude?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Well, I mean -- I'm not dirty.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Are you dirty?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Are you foul-mouthed?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "Yes, I am working on it.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Are you going to try and change that?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "Are you going to try to be better?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Are you sloppy?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Are you sexy?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "You don't think you're sexy?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Well -- I -- I just -- I'm just trying to figure out what to do with what I got.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "What do you think when you look in the mirror?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "Vulnerable?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "You're the best actress in the world right now?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "My pants fell off.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "Well, wait, somebody trips me on the way.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Your pants fell off?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130131pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "Your pants?", "qSentId": 674}]